"以法之名"前情提要...
Previously on damages...
我不知道怎么跟你说
I-I don't know how to tell you this.
不知道什么原因 Ellen进监狱了
Somehow Ellen's in jail.
她因为涉嫌谋杀David被捕
She was arrested for killing David.
David不再爱你了
David doesn't love you anymore.
我和他一直在上床
I've been sleeping with him.
很明显 这女人疯了
Clearly the woman is nuts.
总有解决的办法
There's always a solution.
哪种办法?
What kind of a solution?
一了百了的
A permanent one.
我叫Gregory Malina
My name is Gregory Malina,
我想确保我所叙述的事情
能够公开于众
and I want to make
sure my story gets out.
我收到一封Greg Malina的来信
I got a letter from Greg Malina.
结束了 Art
It's over,Art.
照片把Ray Fiske和
Gregory Malina联系起来
The photos link Ray
Fiske to Gregory Malina,
文件证明Fiske涉嫌内部交易
and the documents prove that
Fiske's guilty of insider trading.
这些证据你应该能用上
You should be able to use that.
你可以回来工作
You can have your job back.
我不想回来
I don't want it.
Gregory?
你在恐吓我 Patty
You're blackmailing me,Patty.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我们真的下半辈子
都得戴着这对戒指?
We really have to wear these
for the rest of our lives?
有些可怕 是吗?
It's kind of terrifying,huh?
不知道
I don't know.
也许我们在犯一个大错
Maybe we're making a big mistake.
什么?
Excuse me?
挑的戒指
About the rings.
也许该选金的
Maybe we should've gone gold.
你笑什么?
What are you smiling at?
等你秃头了 会看起来很性感
You're gonna look sexy when you're bald.
秃头?
Bald?
不可能
No way.
我会一直戴假发
I'm going toupee all the way.
不 别
No,no,don't.
- 为什么?
- 那样不吉利
- Why?
- It's bad luck.
该先把戒指放起来
你弄得我好紧张
We should put them
away,you're making me nervous.
该锁起来
We should lock them up.
戒指还没上保险
They're not insured yet.
谁会拿啊?
Who's gonna take them?
如果收起来 就没人会拿走
No one,if they're hidden.
拜托 亲爱的
那样我就不用老担心
Please,babe,it'll put my mind at ease.
好吧
All right.
钥匙呢?
Do you have your key?
桌上
It's on the desk.
把戒指放在咱们藏东西的地方
Put them in our hiding place.
喂?
Hello?
出什么事了?
What's wrong?
我马上到
I'll be there right away.
谁打来的?
Who was that?
我姐
It was my sister.
她在镇上
She's in the Village.
他们又吵架了
They had another fht.
Patty?
他自杀的
He shot himself.
我要你帮我
I need your help.
-叫警察了吗?
-还没
-Have you called the police?
-Not yet.
还有谁知道?
Who else knows about this?
就我俩
Just us.
拿着
Take this.
放到安全的地方
Put it somewhere safe.
不能让任何人知道
你来这里是为了什么
No one can ever know
what he was doing here.
我明白了
I understand.
连David也不能知道
Not even David.
Ellen?
我能相信你吗?
I can trust you?
能
Yes.
-=伊甸园美剧 http://sfile.ydy.com=-
荣誉出品
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
proudly presents
-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=-
时间轴: 咔肉肉
翻译: elise 泉隽戈泓
校对: sade
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
sync:咔肉肉
以法之名
第一季 第12集
Damages
Season01 Episode12
Parsons 给你安排个狱友
Parsons. Got a roommate.
怎么啦 有钱姑娘?
What's a matter,rich girl?
老爹不肯交保释金?
Daddy won't post bail?
下铺是我的
Lower bunk's mine.
贱人 别以为能和我平起平坐
Bitch,don't even.
他们抓住我之前
我抢了一间便利店和一家红酒店
I ripped off a convenience store and
a bodega before they busted my ass.
我杀了我的未婚夫
I killed my fianc?
一周前
A WEEK EARLIER
亲爱的?
Babe?
- 嘿!
- 嘿
- Hey!
- Hey.
你姐怎么样?
How's your sister?
她没事
Oh,she's fine.
Carrie... 总是麻烦不断
You know,Carrie... it's always a crisis.
你要出去?
You're leaving?
对 刚收到呼叫
Yeah,I just got called in.
等会儿见
I'm gonna see you later.
- 好吗?
- 好的 喂
- Okay?
- Okay.Hey.
我爱你
I love you.
我也爱你
I love you,too.
你怎么认识Raymond Fiske的?
How do you know Raymond Fiske?
Patty?
我们做为控辩双方的律师
正在打一场官司
We were opsing counsel on a case.
谈事儿到这么晚 很经常吗?
Is it common practice to
nduct business this late?
Ray下班前给我打了电话
说他急着见我
Ray called me at the last minute,he
said he needed to see me urgently.
他到之后 发生了什么?
What happened when he got here?
他提出了一项和解协议
He'd proposed a settlement offer.
当我告诉他 我的委托人不接受时
他有些不高兴
When I told him that my clients
didn't accept it,he got upset.
- 他威胁你了吗?
- 没
- Did he threaten you?
- No.
他就起身离开 我...
He just got up and left. I...
以为会晤结束了
I-I thought the meeting was over.
结果他走回来...
But then he came back and,um...
自杀了
did it.
这位女士身上并无火药残留
There are no powder burns on the woman.
血溅的位置 弹道角度 以及尸体位置
Blood spatter,angle of the
trajectory,position of the body.
- 说明这是自杀
- 好的
- This was a suicide.
- Okay.
能带她回家吗?
Can I take her home now?
可以
Yes.
你可以走了 Hewes女士
You're free to go,Ms.Hewes.
不过我们希望如果有什么疑问
能随时找到你
But we'd like you to stay available
in case we have any other questions.
当然
Of course.
喂?
Hello?
什么? 不 慢点说
What? No,slow-slow down.
什么...
What...
你... 什么?
You're... What?
哪里?
Where?
哦...
Well...
天哪 你待在那里多久了?
Jesus Christ. How long have
you been standing out there?
不 等等 稍等
No,no,hold on. Hold on a second.
天哪
Jesus.
Arthur 这是探员Wright和Fleming
Arthur,these are Detectives
Wright and Fleming.
他们有些问题问你
They have a few questions
they need to ask you.
不 不好意思
Nah,excuse me.
Ray在哪里?
But where-where's Ray?
为什么不进来说
Why don't we come inside.
不...
Nah,where...
是关于Ray的事
This is about Ray.
什么意思? 出什么事了?
What do you mean? What happened?
他昨晚自杀了
Last night,he took his own life.
我们有理由相信 他们会面
是为了讨论你这个案子的和解协议
We have reason to believe that they were
meeting to discuss your latest settlement offer.
完全有可能 我们在谈判
That's entirely
possible.We're in negotiations.
你知道昨晚 他们有会晤的计划吗?
Were you aware that there was a
meeting scheduled for last night?
不 我不知道
No. No,I wasn't.
有人告诉Mallory了吗?
Has Mallory been told?
Amos去了
Amos is there now.
我们该陪着她
We should be with her.
Frobisher先生 你最后一次
和Fiske谈话 是什么时候?
Mr.Frobisher,um,when was the last
time that you spoke to Mr.Fiske?
昨天通过电话
Yesterday on the phone.
George Moore死了
George Moore is dead.
我听说了
I heard.
我都不记得我们谈了什么
I don't even really remember
what we were talking about.
谈了些... 可能是案子的细节
Some... probably details
about the,uh,the case.
Fiske先生表现过他很沮丧或者...
Did Mr.Fiske give any indication
that he was distressed or...
没
No.
结束了 Art
It's over,Art.
什么结束了?
What is?
你知道 Fiske的生活中有什么可能
导致他自杀吗?
Are you aware of anything in Mr.Fiske's life
that could have driven him to take this action?
不 什么也没有
No. No,there was nothing.
你没事吧?
You all right?
我没事
I'm fine.
他为什么要自杀?
Why did he do it?
我不知道
I don't know.
当时一定很可怕
Must have been horrible.
我很难过
I'm sorry.
我要你 把事务所暂时关门
I want you to shut down the office.
让大家回家待几天
Send everyone home for a few days.
好的
Okay.
和法官Toomey有个听证会
我要你去接手
There's going to be a hearing with
Judge Toomey. I want you to take it.
我 我会处理好的
I'll,uh,I'll-I'll handle it.
我会离开一阵子
I'll be gone for a while.
没问题
Sure.
需要我做什么尽管说
Anything you need.
谢谢 Tom
Thanks,Tom.
走 小家伙 走
Come on,boy. Comen.
我该取消航班
I think I should cancel my flight.
Phil 去参加你的会议
Aw,Phil,go to your conference.
如果Michael今晚和Henry一家去北部
我就不去参加了
Not if Michael's going upstate
tonight with Henry's family.
我不去也可以 妈妈
I'm happy to bail,Mom.
Henry和我如果去玩 随时可以
Henry and I can go up anytime we want.
不 我不想你们改变计划
No,no,I don't want you
two changing your plans.
Patty 你不能一个人待着
Patty,you shouldn't be alone.
我想静一静
I prefer to be alone.
真的
Really.
你确定?
You sure?
你知道 如果不是 我会告诉你
You ow I'd tell you otherwise.
我想去海滨别墅
I want to go to the beach house.
我想远离这里
I want to get away.
我认识Ray Fiske20多年了
I kneRay Fiske well over 20 years.
一周前
他是个很棒的律师 很好的朋友
A WEEK EARLIER He was a
great lawyer. And a friend.
我们都伤痛欲绝 法官大人
We're all devastated,Your Honor.
我深表同情
You have my sympathies.
发生这样的事
迫使案子的进程暂停
Something like this
happens,it gives us all pause.
不用说 我们得重新组建律师团
Needless to say,we've
been forced to regroup.
新律师刚开始熟悉Frobisher案
New attorneys are just beginning to
familiarize themselves with Mr.Frobisher's case.
对于我予以理解
I appreciate that.
原定下个月底开庭
The trial was set for
the end of next month
我看你请求延期六个月
and I see you're requesting
a six-month extension.
Shayes先生 你的意见?
Mr.Shayes?
首先让我 向你们公司表示哀悼
Well,first of al let me express
my condolences to the entire firm.
我们理解
Phillips先生目前所处的困难境地
We respect the difficult position
Mr.Phillips finds himself in.
也理解让新的团队迅速进入状态
所面临的挑战 但...
We understand the challenge of getting
new team members up to speed,but...
我们的职责则是Frobisher的
5000名付不起账单的员工
our responsibilities lie with Mr.Frobisher's
5,000 employees who can't pay their bills.
对他们而言 延迟审判真是...
For them,justice delayed is truly...
我表示赞同 Phillips先生
I'd have to agree,Mr.Phillips.
有什么提议书吗?
You have a proposed order?
延迟一个月
A one-month continuance.
Phillips先生
法院对你的处境予以理解
Mr.Phillips,the court
empathizes with your position.
谢谢 法官大人
Thank you,Your Honor.
一个月后 我们继续审理
But after one month,we press on.
Ray留了点东西给你
Ray left something for you.
在桌上
It's on the desk.
- Arthur 你慢慢看吧
- 谢谢
- Take your time,Arthur.
- Thank you.
以防我出事 我录了卷带子解释一切
我要你知道 回头是岸 还来得及 Gregory书
In case anything happens to me.I made a videotape explaining everything.I
wanted you to know.There's still time to do the right thing.--Gregory
嘿
Hey.
Ray Fiske昨晚自杀了
Ray Fiske killed himself last night.
新闻都在报
It's all over the news.
我听说了
I heard.
David 怎么了?
David,what is it?
你姐打电话来 看你怎么样
Your sister called to
see how you were doing.
她说这三周没和你打过电话
She said she hasn't spoken
to you in three weeks.
David...
你昨晚去哪里了?
Where were you last night?
你告诉我你被解雇了
You told me that you were fired.
是的 但Patty要我去见George Moore
I was,but Patty needed me
to meet with George Moore.
你没想过该告诉我这些吗?
You didn't think that
you should tell me?
我不想你牵扯进来
I didn't want you involved.
这些人都是危险人物
These people are dangerous.
你知道的越少越好
I thought the less that
you knew,the better.
你从George Moore得到的信息...
This information that you
got from George Moore...
表明Ray Fiske也参与了整个阴谋
Shows that Ray Fiske is
part of the whole conspiracy.
所以Patty用这个威胁Fiske
So Patty used it as
leverage against Fiske.
所以他自杀了?
Is that why he killed himself?
我不知道
I don't know.
Patty那晚恐吓了他
Patty was blackmailing m.
- Fiske涉嫌贪污
- 别...
- Fiske was guilty of corruption.
- Do not...
够了 Ellen!
Enough,Ellen!
David 这些人杀了Gregory Malina
David,listen,these men
killed Gregory Malina.
也很可能杀了George Moore
They probably killed George Moore.
他们为所欲为
They do whatever the hell they want,
除非有人阻止他们
否则他们不会罢手
and they'll keep doing it
until somebody stops them.
Frobisher要负责任
Frobisher has to take responsibility.
打赢官司是唯一的办法
Winning this case is the only
way that that is going to happen.
然后又怎样?
And then what?
你什么意思?
What do you mean?
你要回去给Patty卖命?
Are you going to go back to Patty?
这是我想做的工作 David
This is the kind of work
that I want to do,Dad.
Patty也许是个讨厌鬼 但...
Patty may be a horrible person,but...
那些人更残忍
these guys are ruthless.
我已经不知道你在做什么了
I don't know what you are doing anymore.
我知道自己在做什么
I know exactly what I'm doing.
真的吗?
Really?
现在有人死了 在计划之中?
A man's dead now. Was that thelan?
他们对Katie做出那样的事之后
你们早就该明白
You of all people should understand
after what they did to Katie.
我不管他们 我关心我和你
I don't care about
them; I care about us.
这是代价
This is what it takes.
我不想这样的生活
I don't want this life.
得有人让这些人负责任
Someone has to hold
these guys accountable.
你现在决定 你要我们一起
还是要工作?
You decide right now-- do you
want us or do you want this job?
- 求你别这样
- 现在就决定
- Please don't do this.
- Right now.
现在就决定!
Right now!
你决定不了 对吗?
You can't decide,can you?
- David...
- 不
- No.
我们完了 Ellen
We're done,Ellen.
喂?
Hello?
别说 别说了
Stop,stop it,just stop.
听我说
Listen to me.
该死的 你就不能--不
Damn it,will
you just-- no!
Lila 别再打电话给我
Lila,you need to stop calling me!
很抱歉打搅你了
I'm sorry to disturb you.
你想干吗?
What do you want?
有邻居打电话投诉
Well,one of your neighbors called
刚刚好像听到了争吵
and said they heard a bit
of a commotion earlier.
我只是来看看 你们俩还好吧
I just wanted to make
sure you two are all right.
恩 我们没事
Yeah,we're fine.
你未婚妻在这吗
Is your fiance here?
她出去了
She went out.
一切都好？
But everything's okay?
我们很好
We're great.
- 晚安
- 你也一样
- Have a nice night.
- Hey,you,too.
Malina录了盘该死的录像带
Malina made a goddamn videotape.
在哪
Where is it?
不知道 我不知道
我只知道这带子关乎我的性命
don't know,I don't know,but
right now that tape is my life.
当他回国的时候
Malina去找了那个厨师
When he came back into the
country,Malina went to the ef.
Katie Connor?
你还派人跟着她?
D-Do you still have people on her?
当然
Of course.
好吧 好吧 好吧...
All right,all
right,good,good,good,all right.
你就做你该做的
但要帮我搞到那盘带子
Just do anything you have
to do,but get me that tape.
嘿 是我 我...
Hey,it's me. I...
对不起 请回复我 好吗
I'm so sorry. Just
please call me back.Okay?
老天啊
Jesus Christ.
Katie
Katie.
我能进来吗
Can I come in?
当然
Of course.
我刚刚看到Ellen离开
她好像心情很不好
I just saw Ellen go. She seemed upset.
一切都好吗
Is everything okay?
是的 是的 一切都好
Yeah,yeah,yeah,everything's fine.
好的
Good.
你回来了 你都没打个电话过来
Y-You're bk in town?
Y-You didn't call.
你怎么来这儿了?
What are you doing here?
这是什么
What is this?
Gregory留给我的
Gregory left it with me.
交给Ellen 她得看看
Give it to Ellen. She needs to see this.
好的
Okay.
我要走了
I gotta go.
等等 就这样?
Wait a minute. That's it?
你要走了?
Y-You're leaving?
我都没见你几个月了
I haven't seen you in months.
我不想她回来的时候见到我
I don't want to be
here when she gets back.
我明天电话你
I'll call you tomorrow.
嘿
Hey.
Tom
Tom.
你没事吧
You okay?
嗯 我...
Yeah,I...
我不过是想没人的时候
来拿些东西
I just came by to grab some stuff I thought
it would be better when no one was around.
你听说Fiske的事了吗
You heard about Fiske?
恩 那太糟糕了
Yeah,it's awful.
当着Patty的面那么做
Doing it in front of Patty.
她怎么样了
How is she doing?
她可被吓到了
She's pretty shaken up.
你在 呃 她让走你后见过她吗
Have you seen her
since she,uh,let you go?
我想Patty可不想再看见我
I don't think Patty wants to see me.
- 是啊 你说的那些可是太...
- 愚蠢?
- Yeah,what you said was pretty...
- Stupid?
我想说的是有胆色 但是
呃 是有点蠢
I was going to say
ballsy,but,uh,yeah,stupid...
可以说是"愚蠢"
stupid works.
那么 你知道
我们该什么时候喝杯咖啡
So,uh,you know,we should... we
should gesome coffee sometime.
恩 我很乐意
Yeah,I'd like that.
好的
Okay.
- 保重
- 你也是
- Take care.
- You,too.
谁
Who is it?
Mallory Fiske
Mallory Fiske.
哦 该死
Oh,shit.
Ray有一直在吃药 你知道的
Ray was medicated,you know.
近来这几年一直在服药
For the last several years.
他就是...
He could just get...
有时候非常的抑郁
so depressed sometimes.
你想
Hey,do you want a...
你想喝一杯吗
Do you wanta drink?
- 不 不了 谢谢
- 不要?
- No,no thank you.
- No?
他也许不想让你觉得
有义务处理他的个人问题
Well,he probably didn't want you
feeling obligad to solve his problems.
你了解Ray的
You know Ray.
他会为他在乎的人竭尽全力
He'd bend over backwards to
help someone he cared about,
但老天都不肯让我们任何一个人
担心他的事
but God forbid any of us
should worry about him.
是这样啊 不是吗?
God forbid,right?
案子怎么样了
How was the case going?
顺利
Well.
出乎意料的顺利
Exceptionally well.
Arthur
Ray那天晚上
Arthur,the night Ray,uh...
他
He...
叫我收拾行李
told me to pack my bags.
他说想离开这个国家
Said he wanted to leave the couny.
他那么说了? 为什么
He said that? Why?
我不知道
I don't know.
但是 Arthur
如果这和官司有关的话
But,Arthur,f this had
anything to do with the case...
不 那样我会知道的
No,no,no,no. I-I would have known that.
如果我知道他心里想的是什么
或许我就能...
Maybe if'd understood
him,I could have...
他为什么要那么做
Why did he do it?
Arthur 你比任何人都了解他
Arthur,you knew him better than anyone.
Mallory 和他结婚的是你
我是说
Mallory,you were married
to him. I mean,if you...
如果你不知道他为什么这么做
那么就没有人知道了
if you don't know why
he did this,no one does.
嘿 我 我
Hey,I'm-I'm,uh...
哦 那是啊 很对不起
Oh,sure. I'm so sorry.
对不起
I'm sorry.
- 很对不起占用了你的时间
- 该说对不起的是我
- I'm so sorry to take your time.
- No,no,no,no,no,no,it's me.
呃 你能等一下吗
Uh,can you just hold on one second?
听着 等等 等等...Mallory
Listen,wait,wait. Hold
on,hold on,Mallory.
你对自己如此苛刻
Look,you know,don't-don't
beat yourself up.
你不能责怪自己
You can't blame yourself.
明白吗
You know what I mean?
晚安
Good night.
什么事?
Yeah.
没事  好的 让她们上来
Yeah,no. Good.Send 'em up.
哦 天哪
Oh,Jesus...
晚上好 Parsons小姐
Good evening,Miss Parsons.
- 晚上好 Perry
- 直接上去吧
- Good evening,Perry.
- Go right up.
谢谢
Thank you.
他取消了婚约?
He called off the engagement?
我深表遗憾 Ellen
I'm so sorry,Ellen.
也许我们做的太过分了
Maybe we went too far.
你为我们所做的感到后悔吗
Do you regret what we did?
因为我后悔
Because I do.
你后悔?
You do?
我们违背了原则
We crossed a line.
我们怎么会知道Ray...
How could we know that Ray...
文件还在安全的地方吗
Is the folder in a safe place?
我锁起来了 在我的公寓
It's locked up... in my apartment.
我们周一早上处理它
We'll deal with it on Monday morning.
我走后 你就可以呆在这了
While I'm gone,you're
welcome to stay here.
客房准备好了
The guest room's all made up.
谢谢
Thank you.
你和David之间的问题
可以解决的
You and David can work this out.
我回来时你们要是和好了
我也不会觉得吃惊
I wouldn't be surprised if you were
together again by the time I get back.
就在Fiske先生派我去
佛罗里达安排一个会议后不久
Shortly after,Mr.Fiske sent me to
Florida to help set up a meeting.
我不知道是什么会
I didn't know what
this meeting was about,
但我知道Arthur Frobisher和
一个证交会的人有来往
but I know that Arthur Frobisher was in contact with
a member of the Securities and Exchange Commission.
那个人的名字是
The name of that member is...
George Moore
George Moore.
如果我出了什么事 那一定是George Moore
和Arthur Frobisher所为
If anything happens me,George Moore
and Arthur Frobisher are responsible.
厨房里有波旁威士忌
记得要溜溜Correy
So,there's bourbon in the
kitchen,and remember to walk Cor.
我怎么能找到你
Where can I reach you?
我去海滨小屋 Tom有号儿
I'll be at the beach
house. Tom has the number.
蒙塔克的暴风雨昨晚已经退去
Storm cleared Montauk last night.
这个周末去刚刚好
Should be a perfect weekend.
谢谢 Perry
Thank you,Perry.
Ellen 一切都会好起来的
Ellen,everything's ing to be all right.
嘿 Ellen Ellen 是我
Hey,Ellen,Ellen,it's me.
听着 有些东西你一定得看看
Look,there's something here
that you really got to see.
Katie拿来一盘
Gregory Malina录的带子
Katie brought you a videotape
that Gregory Malina made.
和案子有关
It's about the case.
Gregory坦白了一切在
佛罗里达发生的事情
Gregory confessed everything
about what happened in Florida.
我要上早班 我把它放在
我们的藏东西的地方 好吗
Look,I got the early shift,but I'm
going to leave it in our hiding pla,okay?
天哪!
Shit!
嘿
Hey.
你吓到我了
You scared me.
对不起
Sorry.
我妈妈在哪里
Where's my mom?
她去海滨小屋了
She went to the beach house.
- 她说我可以呆在这的
- 那好
- She said I could stay here.
- Cool.
我只是来拿些东西
I'm just grabbing some stuff.
别和我妈说我来过
Don't tell my mom you saw me.
好的
Sure.
如果有人问起 就说我没来过
If anyone asks,I wasn't here.
对不起 David
I'm sorry,David.
Ellen? 天啊
Ellen? Jesus.
Ellen走了
Ellen's gone.
你怎么会在这儿?
What are you doing here?
- 我给你放水洗澡
- 出去
- I'll run you a bath.
- Just get out of here.
- David 你能...
- 该死的够了
- David,will you...
- Enough of this shit.
- 别这样
- 滚出去
- Don't do this.
- Just get out!
你还没明白我们的感情
You don't know what we had.
我要叫警察了
I'm calling the police
你真该锁上门
You really should lock your door.
- Tom
- 天啊
- Tom.
- Jesus!
Patty 你去哪了
Patty,where the hell have you been?
探亲
Visiting family.
好吧 你得回来
Well,you need to get back here.
Ellen觉得你要杀她
Ellen thinks you tried to kill her.
Patty
Patty?
我就回来
I'm coming home.
Parsons
Parsons.
你被提前释放了
School's out early.
怎么回事?
What's going on?
你被保释了
Your bail was posted.
谁保释的
By who?
一个叫Patricia Hewes的
You know a Patricia Hewes?
好了 你身上原来就
只有一窜钥匙
All right,sweetheart,all
you've got is a set of keys.
你律师给你送了套
换用的衣服
And your attorney sent
you a change of clothes.
在这签名
Sign right here.
也许我该进去
帮你拿点东西 呃?
Oh,maybe I should go in
and get your things,huh?
不了 谢谢
No. Thanks.
我只是想一个人呆会儿
I think I just want to
be alone for a while.
你真该锁上门
You really should lock your door.
那东西在哪儿
Where is it?
录像带在哪儿
Where's the videotape?
查查卧室
Check the bedroom.
找到了吗
What have you got?
把他带过来
Bring him in here.
那该死的录像带 在哪儿
Where... is the goddamn videotape?
我不知道
I don't know.
好的
All right.
我想我找到了些什么
I think I got something.
天啊
Jesus Christ.
带子呢
What about the tape?
不在那里
It wasn't there.
什么
What?
所以我们去了Patty Hewes的公寓
So we went to Patty Hewes' apartment.
然后呢
And?
出了点乱子
Things got a little fouled up.
什么出了点乱子
你这是什么意思?
What the hell is that supposed to
mean,things got a little bit fouled up?
就是说我们没有找到带子
Let's just say we didn't find the tape.
你到底去哪儿了
Where the hell have you been?
Ellen...
不管你是怎么想的
no matter what you think,
我和这没关系
I didn't have anything
to do with any of this.
我知道
I know.
但是Tom说 你指责我要杀害你
But Tom told me that you
accused me of trying to kill you.
我不知道除了这样
怎么才能让你回来
How else was I supposed
to get you back here?
那么这个录像带
So this videotape...
牵涉到Frobisher?
implicates Frobisher?
是的
Yes.
你有条新口讯
You have one new message.
Ellen 是我
Ellen,it's me.
Katie拿来一盘
Gregory Malina录的带子
Katie brought you a videotape
that Gregory Malina made.
我把它放在
我们的藏东西的地方 好吗
I'm going toeave it in
our hiding place,okay?
这就是为什么Frobisher
让人来找这带子
That's why Frobisher had
someone try to find it.
Frobisher的手下没有找到
But Frobisher's people didn't
find the tape in my apartment.
所以他们去了我家
So they went to mine.
但他们不知道我会在那
But they didn't know
at I would be there.
所以他们要杀了你
That's when they tried to kill you.
他们没有找到录像带
但那录像带在哪儿
If they ver found the tape,where is it?
在我手里 在安全的地方
I have it. It's safe.
好的 那我们
Good. Then we...
已经没有什么我们了
There's no we anymore.
我利用这几天仔细考虑过
I've had some time to think
over the past few days.
你雇我的唯一原因就是
为了引Katie作证
The only reason you hired
me was to get to Katie.
- Ellen...
- 别辩解了
- Don't bother.
我老早就参透这件事了
I had that figured out
pretty early actually,
可那之后你又让Tom说服我
让我相信事情并非如此
but then you had Tom
convince me otherwise,
我又傻得相信了他
and I was stupid enough to believe him.
那时候
我没有发现他是个胆小的
At the time,I didn't
alize he's a scared,
软弱的 尽办法讨好你的骗子
weak,liar who would do
anything to please you.
- 我从没有...
- 别扯了
- I would never...
- Bullshit.
然后你又要分开我和David
你把Katie利用好了又丢弃掉
And then you tried to break up me and
David,you trashed Katie as a witness,
你又毫无理由的炒了我
and you fired me for no good reason.
但是你倒给我上了一堂
But you did teach me
one valuable lesson.
我的荣幸
I'm glad.
不要相信任何人
Trust no one.
不再相信任何人 Patty
Well,I don't anymore,Patty.
至少不相信你们这些人
Least of all you.
我明白了
I see...
我会把带子给你
I'll give you the tape...
但是你得先帮我做些事情
but you're going to do
something for me first.
什么
What?
做我的律师
Be my lawyer.
我被控告谋杀 你得还我清白
I've been accused of murder and
you're going to exonerate me.
我需要你的权力和你的关系网
I need your power and your connections.
洗清我的嫌疑
然后帮我找到杀David的人
Clear me of this,and then
help me find who killed David.
如果你这么做的话
If you do that...
我就会给你带子
then I'll give you the tape.
Ellen Parsons被保释出来了
你知道在哪儿能找到她
Ellen********
-------------------------------
本论坛字幕仅翻译交流学习之用
禁止任何商业用途否则后果自负
-------------------------------
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
proudly presents
-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=-
时间轴: 咔肉肉
翻译: elise 泉隽戈泓
校对: sade
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
sync:咔肉肉